Now, let's look at a summary completion exercise
together.
The first step is to read the requirement
to identify the word limit.
The word limit is no more than two
words and or a number.
This means the shortest answer will be one
word or one number.
In step 2, we have to read the
title of the summary to understand the topic
of the recording.
The title is Pinnacle Group Future Plans.
We will listen to the policies regarding the
future directions of Pinnacle Group.
In step 3, we have to read questions,
underline keywords, predict paraphrases of the keywords and what type
of information is missing from each blank.
Remember that in the real listening test, you
will only have about 30 seconds to one
minute for this step before the recording starts.
So it's very important that you practice regularly
to do this quickly and efficiently.
Let's do this step for our exercise.
Great job!
Now you are going to listen and fill
in the correct answers in the practice section.
And don't forget to check your answers carefully
after you complete all the blanks.
See you again soon!